Finding Aid for the World War I and World War II Pamphlet and Newspaper Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
1912-1945
World War I and World War II Pamphlet and Newspaper Collection
MSS.0801
- Lichnowsky, Prince. My Mission to Lincoln: 1912-1914. New York: George H. (Folder 1)
- Duran Company. (Folder 1)
- The War Message and Facts Behind It. Annotated text of President Wilson’s Message: April 2, 1917. Washington: Government Printing Office, 1917. (Folder 2)
- Hazen, Charles D. The Government of Germany. Washington, D.C.: Committee on Public Information, 1917. (Folder 3)
- German War Practices. Issued by the Committee on Public Information. Washington, D.C. January, 1918. (Folder 4)
- Conquest and Kultur: Aims of the Germans in their Own Words. Issued by the Committee on Public Information. Washington, D.C.: January, 1918. (Folder 5)
- Hart, Albert Bushnell, and Arthur O. Lovejoy. Editors. Handbook of the War for Readers, Speakers and Teachers. Issued by the Committee on Public Information. New York: 1918. (Folder 6)
- War Cyclopedia: A Handbook for Ready Reference on the Great War. Washington: Government Printing Office, 1918. (Folder 7)
- Bulletins From Britain. Published by the British Library of Information in New York. June 1942-July 1942. (Folder 8)
- Bulletins From Britain. Published by the British Library of Information in New York July 15, 1942-September 1942. (Folder 9)
- Form One Magazine, Published by the Flying Cadets at Randolph Field, Texas. Merry Christmas issue, December 1940. (Folder 10)
- Camp Edwards News. Published at Camp Edwards at Falmouth, Massachusetts. Volume I. Numbers. 6-12. Falmouth, Massachusetts. (Folder 11)
- Camp Edwards News. Published at Camp Edwards at Falmouth, Massachusetts. Volume I. Numbers 13-20. Falmouth, Massachusetts. (Folder 12)
- Camp Edwards News. Published ad Camp Edwards at Falmouth, Massachusetts. Volume I. Numbers 21-22. Camp Cod, Massachusetts. (Folder 13)
- Form One. Published by the Flying Cadets at Randolph Field, Texas, February-June 1941 (Folder 14)
- Hickam Highlights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, June 1942-July 1942 (Folder 15)
- Hickam Highlights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, July 1942-August 1942 (Folder 16)
- Hickam Highlights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, September 1942-October 1942 (Folder 17)
- Hickam Highlights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, October 1942-November 1942 (Folder 18)
- Hickam Highlights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, January 1943-February 1943 (Folder 19)
- Hickman Highlights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, February 1943-March 1943 (Folder 20)
- Hickman Highlights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, April 1943-May 1943 (Folder 21)
- High-Lights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, May 1943-July 1943 (Folder 22)
- High-Lights. Published at Hickam Field, Hawaii, August 1943-October 1943 (Folder 23)
- The Maple Leaf. A Newspaper for Canadian Forces in Europe, 1943-1945 (Folder 24)
- National Legionnaire. Publication of the American Legion, October 1941 and October 1945 (Folder 25)
- The Stars and Stripes. Newspaper of the U.S. Armed Forces in the European Theater of Operations, April 30, 1945-May 6, 1945 (Folder 26)
- Tennessee Legionnaire. Publication of the American legion, Department of Tennessee, October-December 1941 and February 1942 (Folder 27)
- Yank. An Army Weekly Magazine, November 26, 1944, April 22, 1945, April 29, 1945 (Folder 28)
- 350th Fighter. Published at Camp Gruber, Oklahoma, December 1942-February 1943 (Folder 29)
- 350th Fighter. Published at Camp Gruber, Oklahoma, March 1943-April 1943 (Folder 30)
- 350th Fighter. Published at Camp Gruber, Oklahoma, May 1943-July 1943, October 1943 (Folder 31)
- What’s My Name?, Saturday January 10, 1942 (Folder 32)
- What’s My Name?, Saturday, January 31, 1942 (Folder 33)
- What’s My Name?, Saturday February 7, 1942 (Folder 34)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February, 14, 1942 (Folder 35)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February, 21, 1942 (Folder 36)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 28, 1942 (Folder 37)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 7, 1942 (Folder 38)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 14, 1942 (Folder 39)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 21, 1942 (Folder 40)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 28, 1942 (Folder 41)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 4, 1942 (Folder 42)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 11, 1942 (Folder 43)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 18, 1942 (Folder 44)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 25, 1942 (Folder 45)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 2, 1942 (Folder 46)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 9, 1942 (Folder 47)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 16, 1942 (Folder 48)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 23, 1942 (Folder 49)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 30, 1942 (Folder 50)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 6, 1943 (Folder 51)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 8, 1943 (Folder 52)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 9, 1943 (Folder 53)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 18, 1943 (Folder 54)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 22, 1943 (Folder 55)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 29, 1943 (Folder 56)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 5, 1943 (Folder 57)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 10, 1943 (Folder 58)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 13, 1943 (Folder 59)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 17, 1943 (Folder 60)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 24, 1943 (Folder 61)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 7, 1943 (Folder 62)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 14, 1943 (Folder 63)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 21, 1943 (Folder 64)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 28, 1943 (Folder 65)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 4, 1943 (Folder 66)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 11, 1943 (Folder 67)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 18, 1943 (Folder 68)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 25, 1943 (Folder 69)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 2, 1943 (Folder 70)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 9, 1943 (Folder 71)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 16, 1943 (Folder 72)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 23, 1943 (Folder 73)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 30, 1943 (Folder 74)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 6, 1943 (Folder 75)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 13, 1943 (Folder 76)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 20, 1943 (Folder 77)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 27, 1943 (Folder 78)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 4, 1943 (Folder 79)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 11, 1943 (Folder 80)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 18, 1943 (Folder 81)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 25, 1943 (Folder 82)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 1, 1944 (Folder 83)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 8, 1944 (Folder 84)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 15, 1944 (Folder 85)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 22, 1944 (Folder 86)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 29, 1944 (Folder 87)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 5, 1944 (Folder 88)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 12, 1944 (Folder 89)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 19, 1944 (Folder 90)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 26, 1944 (Folder 91)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 4, 1944 (Folder 92)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 11, 1944 (Folder 93)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 18, 1944 (Folder 94)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 25, 1944 (Folder 95)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 1, 1944 (Folder 96)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 8, 1944 (Folder 97)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 15, 1944 (Folder 98)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 22, 1944 (Folder 99)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 29, 1944 (Folder 100)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 6, 1944 (Folder 101)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 13, 1944 (Folder 102)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 20, 1944 (Folder 103)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 27, 1944 (Folder 104)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 3, 1944 (Folder 105)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 10, 1944 (Folder 106)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 17, 1944 (Folder 107)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 24, 1944 (Folder 108)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 1, 1944 (Folder 109)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 8, 1944 (Folder 110)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 15, 1944 (Folder 111)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 22, 1944 (Folder 112)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 29, 1944 (Folder 113)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 5, 1944 (Folder 114)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 12, 1944 (Folder 115)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 19, 1944 (Folder 116)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 26, 1944 (Folder 116)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 2, 1944 (Folder 117)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 9, 1944 (Folder 118)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 16, 1944 (Folder 119)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 23, 1944 (Folder 120)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 30, 1944 (Folder 121)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 7, 1944 (Folder 122)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 14, 1944 (Folder 123)
- Marine Corps Chevron, October 28, 1944 (Folder 124)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 4, 1944 (Folder 125)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 11, 1944 (Folder 126)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 18, 1944 (Folder 127)
- Marine Corps Chevron, November 25, 1944 (Folder 128)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 2, 1944 (Folder 129)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 9, 1944 (Folder 130)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 16, 1944 (Folder 131)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 23, 1944 (Folder 132)
- Marine Corps Chevron, December 30, 1944 (Folder 133)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 13, 1945 (Folder 134)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 20, 1945 (Folder 135)
- Marine Corps Chevron, January 27, 1945 (Folder 136)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 3, 1945 (Folder 137)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 10, 1945 (Folder 138)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 17, 1945 (Folder 139)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 24, 1945 (Folder 140)
- Marine Corps Chevron, February 17, 1945 (Folder 141)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 3, 1945 (Folder 142)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 10, 1945 (Folder 143)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 24, 1945 (Folder 144)
- Marine Corps Chevron, March 31, 1945 (Folder 145)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 7, 1945 (Folder 146)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 14, 1945 (Folder 147)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 21, 1945 (Folder 148)
- Marine Corps Chevron, April 28, 1945 (Folder 149)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 5, 1945 (Folder 150)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 12, 1945 (Folder 151)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 19, 1945 (Folder 152)
- Marine Corps Chevron, May 26, 1945 (Folder 153)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 2, 1945 (Folder 154)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 9, 1945 (Folder 155)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 16, 1945 (Folder 156)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 23, 1945 (Folder 157)
- Marine Corps Chevron, June 30, 1945 (Folder 158)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 7, 1945 (Folder 159)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 14, 1945 (Folder 160)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 21, 1945 (Folder 161)
- Marine Corps Chevron, July 28, 1945 (Folder 162)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 4, 1945 (Folder 163)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 11, 1945 (Folder 164)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 18, 1945 (Folder 165)
- Marine Corps Chevron, August 25, 1945 (Folder 166)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 1, 1945 (Folder 167)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 15, 1945 (Folder 168)
- Marine Corps Chevron, September 22, 1945 (Folder 169)